Guide to the Duke University Press Records, 1812-2019 UA.07.08.0002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Editorial Files, 1944-2016; 3
  - Woodmansee and Jaszi: Intellectual Propert and the Construction of Authorship, 1992-1993 (Box 302)
    Proposal, reader reports, and correspondence regarding Intellectual Property and the Construction of Authorshp, as well as copies of the Cardozo Arts and Entertainment Law Journal
  - Woodmard, 2006-2009 (Box 335)
  - Woodress, James: American Literacy Scholarship 1987, 1987-1998 (Box 129)
  - Woodson Drexel, 1990-1991 (Box 329)
  - Woolford, Andrew; Colonial Genocide and Indigenous North America, 2013 (Box 124)
  - Woolford, Andrew; Colonial Genocide and Indigenous North America; Contract, 2013 (Box 124)
  - Woolford, Andrew; Colonial Genocide and Indigenous North America; Permissions, 2013 (Box 124)
  - Worham, Erica C.; Video Indigena, 2006-2012 (Box 115)
  - Wright, Christopher; The Echo of Things, 2005-2013 (Box 115)
  - Wright-Rios, 2006-2007 (Box 335)
  - Xiang, Biao; Return, 2011-2012 (Box 115)
  - Xiang, Biao; Return; Permissions, 2012 (Box 115)
  - Xudong, Zhang: Toward an Alternative Modern, 1993-1995 (Box 146)
  - Y. Michael Bodemann; A Jewish Family in Germany Today: An Intimate Portrait, 2004 (Box 95)
  - Y. Michael Bodemann; A Jewish Family in Germany Today: An Intimate Portrait; File 2, 2003-2004 (Box 95)
  - Y. Michael Bodemann; A Jewish Family in Germany Today: An Intimate Portrait; File 3, 2003-2004 (Box 95)
  - Y. Michael Bodemann; Contract, 2003 (Box 95)
  - Yamazaki James, 1994-1995 (Box 323)
  - Yan Hairong, 2004-2009 (Box 296)
  - Yanna Yannakakis, 2000-2007 (Box 298)
  - Yannakakis, Yanna; Indigenous Intellectuals, 2012-2013 (Box 121)
  - Yano, Christine R.; Pink Globalization, 2011-2013 (Box 116)
  - Yano, Christine: Airborne Dreams, 1999-2012 (Box 242)
  - Yarbrough, Tinsley: Mr. Justice Black and His Critics, 1986-1990 (Box 190)
  - Yezierska, Anzia: Arrogant Beggar, 1994-2000 (Box 143)
  - Yinging Reviews Slip Original, 1997-1998 (Box 344)
    Proposal, correspondence, and internal records relating to marketing of AIDS and the National Body
  - Yip, Wai-lim: Chinese Poetry, 1995-2000 (Box 143)
  - Yishai Tobin, 1995-1997 (Box 349)
  - Yoder, Jennifer: From East Germans to Germans?, 1998-1999 (Box 190)
  - Yoshimoto, Mitsuhiro -Kurosawa, 1997-2002 (Box 157)
  - Yuasa Katsuei, 2003-2007 (Box 511)
  - Yudice, George: Stella Manhattan, 1993-1994 (Box 129)
  - Zaborowska, 2007 (Box 304)
  - Zantop, 1997-1998 (Box 345)
  - Zantop, Susanne: Colonial Fantasies, 1995-2000 (Box 130)
  - Zavarzadeh, 1988-1989 (Box 329)
  - Zavella, 2004-2008 (Box 293)
  - Zavella, Pat: Negotiating Mexican Identity, 2008-2010 (Box 242)
  - Zavella. Patricia, 1997-2000 (Box 266)
  - Zerner, Charles: Culture and the Question of Rights, 1999-2003 (Box 227)
  - Zhan Mei, 2006-2010 (Box 334)
  - Zhang, 2002-2008 (Box 298)
  - Zhang Zen, 2002-2006 (Box 289)
  - Zhang, Everett: The Impotence Epidemic: Men's Medicine and Sexual Desire in Contemporary China, 2012-2015 (Box 363)
  - Zhang, Longxi: The Tao and the Logos, 1990-1994 (Box 130)
  - Zhang, Xudong: Chinese Modernism in the Era of Reforms, 1993-1997 (Box 195)
  - Zhang, Xudong: Postmodernism and China, 1997-1999 (Box 190)
  - Zhang, Xudong: Whither China?, 1998-2001 (Box 191)
  - Zhong, Xueping: Masculinity Besieged?, 1997-2000 (Box 157)
  - Ziegler, Heide: Facing Texts, 1985-1998 (Box 191)
  - Zilberg, Elana: Space of Detention, 2007-2011 (Box 248)
  - Zimmermann, Matilde: Sandinista, 1998-2002 (Box 191)
  - Zizek (Box 323)
  - Zizek, Slavoj: Cogito and the Unconscious, 1997-1998 (Box 148)
  - Zoila Mendoza, 2004-2008 (Box 293)
  - Zoltan Zsille, 1986-1989 (Box 329)
  - Zukofsky, 1987-1991 (Box 286)
  - AU: Adams, Vincanne; T: Metrics; ED: Ken Wissoker, Spring 2016 (Box 378)
  - AU: Amrute, Sareeta; T: Encoding Race, Encoding Class; ED: Ken Wissoker, Fall 2016 (Box 373)
  - AU: Bailey, Robert; Art & Language International; ED: Ken Wissoker, Spring 2016 (Box 378)
  - AU: Balance, Christine Bacareza; T: Tropical Renditions; ED: Ken Wissoker, Spring 2016 (Box 378)
  - AU: Bassi, Ernesto; T: Aqueous Territory; ED: Gisela Fosado, Fall 2016 (Box 377)
  - AU: Bennett, Tony; Cameron, Fiona; Dias, Nélia; Dibley, Ben; Harrison, Rodney; Jacknis, Ira; McCarthy, Conal; T: Collecting, Ordering, Governing; ED: Ken Wissoker, Fall 2016 (Box 373)
  - AU: Besteman, Catherine; T: Making Refuge; ED: Gisela Fosado, Spring 2016 (Box 371)
  - AU: Biddle, Jennifer Loureide; T: Remote Avante Garde; ED: Ken Wissoker, Spring 2016 (Box 378)
  - AU: Briggs, Charles L.; Mantini-Briggs, Clara; T: Tell Me Why My Children Died; ED: Ken Wissoker, Spring 2016 (Box 378)
  - AU: Butler, Judith; Gambetti, Zeynep; Sabsay, Leticia; T: Vulnerability in Resistance; ED: Courtney Berger, Fall 2016 (Box 376)
  - AU: Cai Xiang; T: Revolution and its Narratives; ED: Ken Wissoker, Spring 2016 (Box 378)
  - AU: Chafe, William H; T: Hillary and Bill; ED: Gisela Fosado, Spring 2016 (Box 371)
  - AU: Chappell, David L.; T: Waking from the Dream; ED: Gisela Fosado, Spring 2016 (Box 371)
  - AU: Cheah, Pheng; T: What is a World?; ED: Courtney Berger, Spring 2016 (Box 370)
  - AU: Chin, Elizabeth; T: My Life with Things; ED: Ken Wissoker, Spring 2016 (Box 378)
  - AU: Ciccariello-Maher, George; T: Decolonizing Dialectics; ED: Courtney Berger, Fall 2016 (Box 376)
  - AU: Coffman, Tom; T: Nation Within; ED: Gisela Fosado, Fall 2016 (Box 377)
  - AU: Coles, Romand; T: Visionary Pragmatism; ED: Courtney Berger, Spring 2016 (Box 370)
  - AU: Comella, Lynn; T: Vibrator Nation; ED: Ken Wissoker, Fall 2016 (Box 373)
  - AU: Coutin, Susan Bibler; T: Exiled Home; ED: Gisela Fosado, Spring 2016 (Box 371)
  - AU: Critical Ethnic Studies Editorial Collective: T: Critical Ethnic Studies; ED: Courtney Berger, Spring 2016 (Box 370)
  - AU: Crowley-Matoka, Megan; T: Domesticating Organ Transplant; ED: Ken Wissoker, Spring 2016 (Box 378)
  - AU: Day, Iyko; T: Alien Capital; ED: Courtney Berger, Spring 2016 (Box 370)
  - AU: Eddy, Chuck; T: Terminated for Reasons of Taste; ED: Ken Wissoker, Fall 2016 (Box 373)
  - AU: Eller, Anne; T: We Dream Together; ED: Gisela Fosado, Fall 2016 (Box 377)
  - AU: Ferreira, Gloria; Herkenhoff, Paulo; T: Mario Pedrosa; ED: Ken Wissoker, Spring 2016 (Box 378)
  - AU: Fiol-Matta, Licia; T: Great Woman Singer; ED: Ken Wissoker, Fall 2016 (Box 373)
  - AU: Fontes, Paulo; T: Migration and the Making of Industrial Sao Paulo; ED: Gisela Fosado, Spring 2016 (Box 371)
  - AU: Forsdick, Charles; Høgsbjerg, Christian; T: Black Jacobins Reader; ED: Gisela Fosado, Fall 2016 (Box 377)
  - AU: Frost, Samantha; T: Biocultural Creatures; ED: Courtney Berger, Spring 2016 (Box 370)
  - AU: Fuhrmann, Arnika; T: Ghostly Desires; ED: Ken Wissoker, Spring 2016 (Box 378)
  - AU: García-Peña, Lorgia; T: Borders of Dominicanidad; ED: Courtney Berger, Fall 2016 (Box 376)
  - AU: Ghosh, Ranjan; Miller, J. Hillis; T: Thinking Literature Across Continents; ED: Courtney Berger, Fall 2016 (Box 376)
  - AU: Gill, Lesley; T: Century of Violence in a Red City; ED: Gisela Fosado, Spring 2016 (Box 371)
  - AU: Gillespie, Michael Boyce; T: Film Blackness; ED: Ken Wissoker, Fall 2016 (Box 373)
  - AU: Goldberg, Jonathan; T: Melodrama; ED: Ken Wissoker, Fall 2016 (Box 373)
  - AU: Goldstein, Daniel M; T: Owners of the Sidewalk; ED: Gisela Fosado, Spring 2016 (Box 372)
  - AU: Greene, Shane; T: Punk and Revolution; ED: Gisela Fosado, Fall 2016 (Box 377)
  - AU: Hall, Stuart; T: Cultural Studies 1983; ED: Ken Wissoker, Fall 2016 (Box 373)
  - AU: Hanna, Monica; Harford Vargas, Jennifer; Saldívar, José David; T: Junot Diaz and the Decolonial Imagination; ED: Ken Wissoker, Spring 2016 (Box 379)
  - AU: Haraway, Donna J; T: Staying with the Trouble; ED: Ken Wissoker, Fall 2016 (Box 373)
  - AU: Hasso, Frances S; Salime, Zakia; T: Freedom without Permission; ED: Courtney Berger, Fall 2016 (Box 376)
  - AU: Hearn, Adrian H; T: Diaspora and Trust; ED: Gisela Fosado, Spring 2016 (Box 372)
  - AU: Hinton, Alexander Laban; T: Man or Monster?; ED: Gisela Fosado, Fall 2016 (Box 377)
  - AU: Hogan, Kristen; T: Feminist Bookstore Movement; ED: Courtney Berger, Spring 2016 (Box 370)
  - AU: Imre, Anikó; T: TV Socialism; ED: Ken Wissoker, Spring 2016 (Box 379)
  - AU: INCITE!; T: Color of Violence; ED: Elizabeth Ault, Fall 2016 (Box 376)
  - AU: Ingersoll, Karin Amimoto; T: Waves of Knowing; ED: Ken Wissoker, Fall 2016 (Box 373)
  - AU: Johnson, E. Patrick; Rivera-Servera, Ramón H; T: Blacktino Queer Performance; ED: Courtney Berger, Spring 2016 (Box 370)
  - AU: Johnson, E. Patrick; T: No Tea, No Shade; ED: Courtney Berger, Fall 2016 (Box 376)
  - AU: Jones, Hettie; T: Love, H; ED: Ken Wissoker, Fall 2016 (Box 373)
  - AU: Kaczynski, David; T: Every Last Tie; ED: Gisela Fosado, Spring 2016 (Box 372)
  - AU: Karush, Matthew B; T: Musicians in Transit; ED: Gisela Fosado, Fall 2016 (Box 377)
  - AU: Kazanjian, David; T: Brink of Freedom; ED: Ken Wissoker, Spring 2016 (Box 379)
  - AU: Kim, Eunjung; T: Curative Violence; ED: Elizabeth Ault, Fall 2016 (Box 376)
  - AU: Kimura, Aya Hirata; T: Radiation Brain Moms and Citizen Scientists; ED: Courtney Berger, Fall 2016 (Box 376)
  - AU: Kockelman, Paul; T: Chicken and the Quetzal; ED: Gisela Fosado, Spring 2016 (Box 372)
  - AU: Kuoni, Carin; Haines, Chelsea; T: Entry Points; ED: Courtney Berger, Spring 2016 (Box 370)
  - AU: Lawrence, Tim; T: Life and Death on the New York Dance Floor, 1980–1983; ED: Ken Wissoker, Fall 2016 (Box 374)
  - AU: Lazarre, Jane; T: Beyond the Whiteness of Whiteness; ED: Miriam Angress, Spring 2016 (Box 372)
  - AU: Lee, Charles T.; T: Ingenious Citizenship; ED: Courtney Berger, Spring 2016 (Box 371)
  - AU: Lee, Doreen; T: Activist Archives; ED: Ken Wissoker, Spring 2016 (Box 379)
  - AU: Lewis, Tania; Martin, Fran; Sun, Wanning; T: Telemodernities; ED: Ken Wissoker, Fall 2016 (Box 374)
  - AU: Llamojha Mitma, Manuel; Heilman, Jaymie Patricia; T: Now Peru is Mine; ED: Gisela Fosado, Fall 2016 (Box 377)
  - AU: Manning, Erin; T: Minor Gesture; ED: Ken Wissoker, Spring 2016 (Box 379)
  - AU: Mansoor, Jaleh; T: Marshall Plan Modernism; ED: Ken Wissoker, Fall 2016 (Box 374)
  - AU: Mercer, Kobena; T: Travel & See; ED: Ken Wissoker, Spring 2016 (Box 379)
  - AU: Messeri, Lisa; T: Placing Outer Space; ED: Ken Wissoker, Fall 2016 (Box 374)
  - AU: Okihiro, Gary Y; T: Third World Studies; ED: Ken Wissoker, Fall 2016 (Box 374)
  - AU: Ong, Aihwa; T: Fungible Life; ED: Ken Wissoker, Fall 2016 (Box 374)
  - AU: Pandian, Anand; McLean, Stuart; T: Crumpled Paper Boat; ED: Ken Wissoker, Spring 2016 (Box 379)
  - AU: Pierce, Steven; T: Moral Economies of Corruption; ED: Miriam Angress, Spring 2016 (Box 372)
  - AU: Piot, Charles; T: Doing Development in Africa; ED: Ken Wissoker, Fall 2016 (Box 374)
  - AU: Pitts-Taylor, Victoria; T: Brain's Body; ED: Courtney Berger, Spring 2016 (Box 371)
  - AU: Povinelli, Elizabeth A; T: Geontologies; ED: Ken Wissoker, Fall 2016 (Box 374)
  - AU: Price, David H; T: Cold War Anthropology; ED: Ken Wissoker, Spring 2016 (Box 379)
  - AU: Probyn, Elspeth; T: Eating the Ocean; ED: Ken Wissoker, Fall 2016 (Box 374)
  - AU: Puri, Jyoti; T: Sexual States; ED: Ken Wissoker, Spring 2016 (Box 379)
  - AU: Rafael, Vicente L; T: Motherless Tongues; ED: Ken Wissoker, Spring 2016 (Box 379)
  - AU: Randall, Margaret; T: Only the Road / Solo el Camino; ED: Gisela Fosado, Fall 2016 (Box 377)
  - AU: Rawat, Ramnarayan S.; Satyanarayana, K.; T: Dalit Studies; ED: Miriam Angress, Spring 2016 (Box 372)
  - AU: Roberts, Brian Russell; Foulcher, Keith; T: Indonesian Notebook; ED: Courtney Berger, Spring 2016 (Box 371)
  - AU: Rojas, Carlos; Litzinger, Ralph A; T: Ghost Protocol; ED: Ken Wissoker, Fall 2016 (Box 374)
  - AU: Salvatore, Ricardo D.; T: Disciplinary Conquest; ED: Miriam Angress, Spring 2016 (Box 372)
  - AU: Sanabria, Emilia; T: Plastic Bodies; ED: Ken Wissoker, Spring 2016 (Box 380)
  - AU: Schoonover, Karl; Galt, Rosalind; T: Queer Cinema in the World; ED: Courtney Berger, Fall 2016 (Box 376)
  - AU: Seltzer, Mark; T: Official World; ED: Ken Wissoker, Spring 2016 (Box 380)
  - AU: Sharpe, Christina; T: In the Wake; ED: Ken Wissoker, Fall 2016 (Box 375)
  - AU: Siddall, Gillian; Waterman, Ellen; T: Negotiated Moments; ED: Ken Wissoker, Spring 2016 (Box 380)
  - AU: Smith, Terry; T: One and Five Ideas; ED: Ken Wissoker, Fall 2016 (Box 375)
  - AU: Snyderman, Ralph; T: Chancellor's Tale; ED: Miriam Angress, Fall 2016 (Box 372)
  - AU: Spencer, Robyn C; T: Revolution has Come; ED: Gisela Fosado, Fall 2016 (Box 377)
  - AU: Stoler, Ann Laura; T: Duress; ED: Ken Wissoker, Fall 2016 (Box 375)
  - AU: Tapscott, Horace; T: Songs of the Unsung; ED: Ken Wissoker, Fall 2016 (Box 375)
  - AU: Tate, Greg; T: Flyboy 2; ED: Ken Wissoker, Fall 2016 (Box 375)
  - AU: Taylor, Diana; Novak, Lorie; T: Dancing with the Zapatistas; ED: Ken Wissoker, Spring 2016 (Box 380)
  - AU: Taylor, Diana; Steuernagel, Marcos; T: What is Performance Studies?; ED: Ken Wissoker, Spring 2016 (Box 380)
  - AU: Taylor, Dorceta E; T: Rise of the American Conservation Movement; ED: Courtney Berger, Fall 2016 (Box 376)
  - AU: Tutino, John; T: New Countries; ED: Gisela Fosado, Fall 2016 (Box 377)
  - AU: van der Veer, Peter; T: Value of Comparison; ED: Ken Wissoker, Spring 2016 (Box 380)
  - AU: Walker, Gavin; T: Sublime Pervision of Capital; ED: Ken Wissoker, Spring 2016 (Box 380)
  - AU: Weiss, Brad; T: Real Pigs; ED: Ken Wissoker, Fall 2016 (Box 375)
  - AU: Weston, Kath; T: Animate Planet; ED: Ken Wissoker, Fall 2016 (Box 375)
  - AU: White, Geoffrey M; T: Memorializing Pearl Harbor; ED: Ken Wissoker, Spring 2016 (Box 380)
  - AU: Willey, Angela; T: Undoing Monogamy; ED: Courtney Berger, Spring 2016 (Box 371)
  - AU: Winters, Joseph R; T: Hope Draped in Black; ED: Miriam Angress, Spring 2016 (Box 372)
  - AU: Yoneyama, Lisa; T: Cold War Ruins; ED: Ken Wissoker, Fall 2016 (Box 375)
  - AU: Youngmin Choe; T: Tourist Distractions; ED: Courtney Berger, Spring 2016 (Box 370)
  - AU: Zeiderman, Austin; T: Endangered City; ED: Gisela Fosado, Spring 2016 (Box 372)
- Author Files, 1933-1965; 4
  This series consists of correspondence with authors and publicity material related to the publication of individual books. Includes reviews, requests for review copies, lists of who should receive review copies, and correspondence with authors regarding publicity efforts. Mainly correspondence of the publicity director.
  - Acomb, Frances (Anglophobia in France, 1763-1789), 1948-1950 (Box 6)
  - Bevington, Merle (Matthew Arnold's England and the Italian Question), 1952-1953 (Box 6)
  - Blackburn, William (One and Twenty), 1945-1952 (Box 6)
  - Blackburn, William (Joseph Conrad), 1958-1959 (Box 6)
  - Blomquist, Hugo L. (A Manual of the Grasses of North Carolina), 1948-1950 (Box 6)
  - Boyd, William Kenneth (Historical Papers of Trinity College Historical Society), 1939-1951 (Box 6)
  - Bradway, John S. (Duke Legal Aid Clinic Handbook), 1945-1955 (Box 6)
  - Brinkley, R. Florence (Coleridge on the 17th Century), 1955-1957 (Box 6)
  - Cahoon, John B. (Formulating X-Ray Technics), 1957-1965 (Box 6)
  - Cartwright, W.H. and W.B. Hamilton (Duke Centennial Conference On Teacher Training), 1953 (Box 6)
  - Chaffin, Nora B. (Trinity College), 1947-1962 (Box 6)
  - Clyde, Paul Hibbert (U.S. Policy Toward China), 1940-1942 (Box 6)
  - Cole, Taylor (The Canadian Bureaucracy), 1949-1952 (Box 6)
  - Crowell, John Franklin (Personal Recollections), 1938-1939 (Box 6)
  - Davis, Thomas B. (Carlos De Alvear), 1953-1955 (Box 6)
  - Dowd, Jerome (Life of Braxton Craven), 1938-1939 (Box 6)
  - Elliott, George Roy (Scourge and Minister), 1951-1952 (Box 6)
  - Elliott, George Roy (Flaming Minister), 1952-1956 (Box 6)
  - Ellwood, Charles A. (Methods in Sociology), 1933-1939 (Box 6)
  - Gohdes, Clarence and R.G. Silver (Faint Clews and Indirections), 1948-1950 (Box 6)
  - Gohdes, Clarence and R.G. Silver (Faint Clews and Indirections), (Material for Circular and Jacket), 1948-1950 (Box 6)
  - Hamilton, William B. (50 Years of South Atlantic Quarterly), 1952-1953 (Box 6)
  - Hamilton, William B. (Anglo-American Law on the Frontier), 1954-1955 (Box 6)
  - Hendricks, W.C. (Bundle of Troubles), 1944-1945 (Box 6)
  - Hubbell, Jay (The South in American Literature), 1941-1955 (Box 6)
  - Judd, C.H. and others (A Century of Social Thought), 1939-1941 (Box 6)
  - Lemkin, Raphael and McDermott (Polish Penal Code of 1932), 1939-1940 (Box 6)
  - Lobonov-Rostovsky, Andrew (Russia and Europe), 1943-1950 (Box 6)
  - London, Fritz (Superfluids), 1958 (Box 6)
  - Mabry, William A. (The Negro in North Carolina Politics Since Reconstruction), 1940-1943 (Box 6)
  - McDougall, William (Religion and the Sciences of Life), 1935-1937 (Box 6)
  - Parker, Harold T. (Three Napoleonic Battles), 1943-1946 (Box 6)
  - Pearse, A.S. (Migrations of Animals from Sea to Land), 1937-1941 (Box 6)
  - Robert, Joseph Clark (The Tobacco Kingdom), 1938-1939 (Box 6)
  - Roper, Daniel C. (50 Years of Public Life), 1941-1943 (Box 6)
  - Sydnor, Charles S. (Gentleman of the Old Natchez Region), 1938-1940 (Box 6)
  - Tilley, Nannie (Guide to Manuscript Collections in the Duke University Library), 1944-1948 (Box 6)
  - White, Newman I., and others (Frank C. Brown's Folklore), 1951-1955 (Box 6)
  - Miscellaneous, 1949-1956 (Box 6)
- Subject Files, 1942-1976; 5
  Arranged alphabetically by subject, this series includes advertisements for publications, annual reports and correspondence from Ashbel Brice to President Knight, agendas, correspondence, and memoranda for meetings of the Southern University Presses.
  Also included is correspondence showing how inquiries about manuscript publication was handled during the 1940s and 1950s. There are also files on manuscripts possible, mansucripts unlikely, manuscripts rejected, and permission to quote from articles or books. This material has been sampled and around 20% retained.
  - Activities/Reports, 1961-1962 (Box 7)
  - Advertisements (A-R), circa 1963-1964 (Box 7)
  - Advertisements (S-Z), circa 1963-1964 (Box 7)
  - Lilly Endowment Research Series advertisements, circa 1964-1965 (Box 7)
  - American Book Publishers Council, Inc., 1961-1968 (Box 7)
  - Congressional Research Service (A. Brice), 1971-1975 (Box 7)
  - Law and Contemporary Problems, 1976 (Box 7)
  - Manuscript Inquiries (sample), 1945-1947 (Box 7)
  - Manuscript Inquiries, 1946-1947 (Box 7)
  - Manuscript Inquiries (sample), 1947-1949 (Box 7)
  - Manuscripts possible (sample), 1951-1956 (Box 7)
  - Manuscripts received in office (sample), 1945-1947 (Box 7)
  - Manuscripts received (sample), 1952-1954 (Box 7)
  - Manuscripts rejected (sample), 1942-1943 (Box 7)
  - Manuscripts rejected (sample), 1953-1956 (Box 7)
  - Manuscripts unlikely (sample), 1952-1956 (Box 7)
  - Miscellaneous subjects (identified), 1968-1974 (Box 7)
  - Miscellaneous subjects, 1974-1975 (Box 7)
  - Permissions (to quote, etc.) (sample), 1953-1956 (Box 7)
  - Reports, correspondence- Brice to President Knight (folder 1), 1963-1969 (Box 7)
  - Reports, correspondence- Brice to President Knight (folder 2), 1963-1969 (Box 7)
  - Southern University Presses- meetings, 1971-1972 (Box 7)
  - Southern University Presses- meetings, 1968-1970 (Box 7)
- Financial Records, 1926-1968; 6
  This series includes detailed financial information, primarily annual reports, showing income and expenses for a given fiscal year. The material is often broken down between books and journals and occasionally documents how well individual books did also.
  - Financial Records, 1951-1952 (Box 7)
  - Financial Records, 1953-1954 (Box 7)
  - Financial Records, 1954-1955 (Box 7)
  - Financial Records, 1955-1956 (Box 7)
  - Financial Records, 1956-1957 (Box 7)
  - Financial Records, 1957-1958 (Box 7)
  - Financial Records, 1958-1959 (Box 7)
  - Financial Records, 1959-1960 (Box 7)
  - Financial Records, 1960-1961 (Box 7)
  - Financial Records, 1961-1962 (Box 7)
  - Financial Records, 1962-1963 (Box 7)
  - Financial Records, 1963-1964 (Box 7)
  - Financial Records (yearly book sales report), 1964-1965 (Box 7)
  - Financial Records (yearly book sales report), 1956-1966 (Box 7)
  - Financial Records (yearly book sales report), 1966-1967 (Box 7)
  - Financial Records, undated (Box 7)
  - Financial Records, estimates on never published manuscripts, 1961 (Box 7)
  - Financial Records, Printing Lists, 1959-1965 (Box 7)
  - Financial Records, Printing Lists, 1966-1968 (Box 7)
  - Financial Records, Income/Sales reports, graphs, 1956-1960 (Box 7)
  - Financial Records, audit, 1959-1960 (Box 7)
  - Financial Records, Sale reports, 1958 July-1962 February (Box 7)
  - Financial Records, miscellaneous (Box 8 (oversized material))
  - Financial Records, 1926/1927-1939/1940 (Box 8 (oversized material))
  - Detailed Financial Statements, 1959-1960 (Box 8 (oversized material))
  - Detailed Financial Statements, 1958-1959 (Box 8 (oversized material))
  - Detailed Financial Statements (two folders), 1957-1958 (Box 8 (oversized material))
  - Detailed Financial Statements, 1956-1957 (Box 8 (oversized material))
  - Duke University Press Account Book, 1925-1946 (Box 10)
- Catalogs, 1929-1989; 7
  This series contains announcements, catalogs and trade lists advertising upcoming and current publications by Duke University Press.
  - Catalogs, Announcements, 1959 (Box 9)
  - Catalogs, Announcements, 1960-1969 (Box 9)
  - Catalogs, Announcements, 1970-1979 (Box 9)
  - Catalogs, Announcements, 1980-1989 (Box 9)
  - Catalogs, Announcements, undated (Box 9)
  - Duke University Press Catalogues, 1926-1959 (Box 9)
  - Duke University Press Catalogues and Trade Lists, 1960-1964 (Box 9)
  - Duke University Press Catalogues and Trade Lists, 1965-1969 (Box 9)
  - Duke University Press Catalogues and Trade Lists, 1970-1979 (Box 9)
  - Duke University Press Catalogues and Trade Lists, 1980-undated (Box 9)
  - Duke University Press Catalogues and Trade Lists, 1987-1989 (Box 9)
  - Catalogs, Journals (Box 9)
  - Catalogs, Trade Lists, 1924-1959 (Box 9)
- Association of American University Presses, 1948-1957; 8
  The Association of American University Presses is a professional organization whose membership consists of University presses or publishers. The material relates to Duke University Press' membership to the AAUP and includes correspondence, memoranda, annual meeting minutes, questionnaires and a survey.
  - Minutes of the Annual Meeting of the Association of American University Presses, 1948 June 21-22 (Box 9)
  - Minutes of the Annual Meeting of the Association of American University Presses, 1949 May 9-11 (Box 9)
  - Minutes of the Annual Meeting of the Association of American University Presses, 1950 May 7-9 (Box 9)
  - Minutes of the 21st Anniversary Meeting of the Association of American University Presses, 1952 June 15-17 (Box 9)
  - Minutes of the 22nd Annual Meeting of the Association of American University Presses, 1953 April 12-14 (Box 9)
  - Minutes of the Annual Meeting of the Association of American University Presses, 1954 May 2-4 (Box 9)
  - Minutes of the 24th Annual Meeting of the Association of American University Presses, 1955 July 18-20 (Box 9)
  - Minutes of the 26th Annual Meeting of the Association of American University Presses, 1957 May 5-7 (Box 9)
  - Survey of University Presses, 1948-1949 (Box 9)
  - Survey of University Presses, 1948-1951 (Box 9)
  - Association of American University Presses, 1949-1950 (Box 9)
  - Association of American University Presses, 1951-1952 (Box 9)
  - Association of American University Presses, 1951-1952 (Box 9)
  - Association of American University Presses, 1952 (Box 9)
  - Association of American University Presses, 1953 (Box 9)
  - Association of American University Presses, 1954-1955 (Box 9)
- Carlyle Letters, 1812-1856; 9